Seina-chan,
せいなちゃん、
It's been a long time.
め っちゃ久々だね
Have you become a bit more mature?
ちょっと大人っぽくなった?
Is it because it's my private clothes?
私服だからか
Isn't plain clothes erotic?
私服エロくない?
Are you wearing underwear?
下履いてる?
I'm wearing it.
履いてる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
What is this?
これ何これ?
This, this, this.
これこれこれ
This is complicated.
これこじこじ
Do you know?
知ってる?
i don't know.
知らない
Because the Cyboom is coming.
めっちゃサイブーム来てるから
Seina-chan, you graduated, right?
せいなちゃん、卒業したっしょ?
I graduated.
卒業しました
During this time?
この間?
Congratulations.
おめでとう
it was fun?
楽しかった?
school life.
学校生活
Haran was perfect.
ハラン万丈だった
Were you able to graduate safely?
無事卒業はできたの?
It's okay, just in case.
無 事、一応一応
That was good.
良かったね
It was really good.
めっちゃ良かったじゃん
Is it okay if you come to the graduation celebration?
卒業祝いに出てくれるってことで大丈夫?
It's a graduation celebration.
卒業祝いということで
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
You can eat it, right?
食べれるでしょ
You can eat sushi, right?
お寿司食べれるでしょ
Wouldn't it be nice to have sushi that doesn't turn around?
回らないお寿司がいいでしょ?
Sushi that doesn't go around.
回らないお寿司
Should I give you more money?
あとお金いっぱい渡せばいいんでしょ?
Will you come out then?
それしたら出てくれるんでしょ?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
Okay, okay, okay.
オッケーオッケーオッケー
I wanted to wear a little uniform.
制服ちょっとね、着たかったね
I wanted to wear it.
着たかった
Maybe next time I'll take a photo in uniform.
今度制服で撮ろうかな
It might be kind of embarrassing.
なんか恥ずかしいかも
why?
なんで?
After all, right?
だってこの間でしょ?
I graduated.
卒業したの
Because I'm not active.
現役じゃないから
Because I can't call myself JK.
JK名乗れないから
Seriously?
マジ?
By the way.
ちなみにさ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
A little service shot.
ちょろっとサービスショット
Okay.
いいよ
I'm wearing them properly.
ちゃんと履いてるんだ
ちゃん と履いてるんだ
cute.
かわいい
What should I do?
どうしようかな?
Are you going to the aquarium?
水族館行く?
i wanna go.
行きたい
Well then, let's go to the aquarium.
じゃあちょっと水族館行こうか
Shall we go?
行こうか
Do you know where the aquarium is?
水族館どっか分かる?
There's a lot of clatter.
ガチャガチャあるよ
I want to do it.
やりたい
I want to play gacha gacha.
こじこじのガチャガチャやりたい
do?
やる?
Let's go then.
じゃあ行こう
Is there any?
あるかな?
Kojikoji.
こじこじ
What is it?
なんなの?
Pry.
こじこじって
Because it's famous.
有名だから
this?
これ?
Really famous.
本当に有名
Seriously?
マ ジで?
cute.
かわいい
I'm more interested in Sena-chan than that kind of prank.
俺はさ、そんなこじこじよりさ、 せなちゃんの方が興味あるから
difference.
さ
No, no, I'm curious about it.
いや いや、こじこじに興味持って
Really.
本当に
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Because there are a lot of people.
いっぱい人いるからさ
Because it hasn't fallen off that much.
あんま落ちてないからさ
there were?
あった?
be?
ある?
Anno?
あんの?
Oh, hey.
え、なぁ
be?
ある?
there were.
あった
Kojikoji.
こじこじ
which one?
どれ?
this.
これ
How much is it once?
一回いくら?
300 yen?
300円?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 600 yen.
1、2、3、4、5、6、 600円
Can I do it twice?
2回やっていいの?
Will it come out?
出るかな?
Because this is what I want the most.
これが一番欲しいから
Have you ever played Gacha Gacha?
ガチャガチャとかしたことあるの?
I was messing around.
めちゃめちゃやってた
Eh, that's cute.
え、かわいい
Did you do it?
できた?
Can you open it?
開けれる?
I think I can open it.
開けると思う
You can open it.
開けていいよ
Did you find what you want?
欲しいの出てきた?
Jiro-kun came out.
ジローくん出てきた
this.
これ
Well then, let's try it again.
じゃあもう一回やんなよ
Will it come out?
出るかな?
this.
これ
Doesn't it come out?
出てこない?
That's it again this time.
また 今度のあれだね
But, is this no good?
だけどさ、これではダメなの?
This is nice in a pinch.
こじこじでこれがいい
Was Kojikoji-kun good?
こじこじくんがよかったの?
Shall we do it again?
もう一回やる?
Is it okay?
いいの?
I want to eat sushi and I want to eat fish.
お寿司食べたいし、魚食べたい
OK
So let's go to the aquarium.
じゃあ水族館行こうか
what?
何?
It's not moving.
動いてない
Look this way.
こっち向いて
I'm glad I came to the aquarium, but I'm not allowed to take pictures.
水族館来たのはいいけどさ、 撮影もダメだしさ、
It's extremely dark.
めちゃめちゃ暗いしさ
What should I do?
どうする?
Follow me a little further.
もうちょっと追って行って
Apparently it's not allowed to take pictures?
撮影ダメらしい?
Don't you feel a little naughty when it's dark like this?
こんなさ、暗いとさ、 ちょっとイッチな気分になってこない?
It's coming.
なってくる
What's coming?
な ってくる?
I'm glad you came to the aquarium.
水族館来たのはいいけどね
ERROR
じゃあまた撮影できるところを 探して撮影するね
I took a photo.
撮影しちゃった
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
It's creepy in the back.
奥のキモい
I feel like I'm not working.
仕事してない感が
It feels amazing not to be working.
仕事してない感すごい
Saborima.
サボリマ
Doesn't it look delicious?
美味しそうじゃない?
Looks like white fish.
白身魚っぽい
It looks a lot like white fish.
めっちゃ白身魚っぽい
It looks delicious though.
普通に美味しそうなんだけど
Maybe I'll show you the camera.
ちょっとカメラ見せるかもしれない
Sena-chan is cute.
セナちゃんかわいいね
What do you want to see at the aquarium?
水族館で何見たいの?
I saw Mambo.
マンボ見たの
Do you want to see Mambo?
マンボ見たいの?
Is there a mambo?
マンボいるの?
Do you like mambo?
マンボ好きなの?
I love mambo.
マンボ大好き
Are you going to see Mambo?
マンボ見に行く?
ERROR
マンボ見に行こうか
Sena-chan, if it wasn't for Mambo,
セナちゃん、マンボもいなければさ、
I couldn't take any pictures at all because it was all in dark places.
暗いところばっかりでさ、 全然撮影できなかったんだけど
Well, I got to see a lot of the store staff.
まぁでも、店員さんいっぱい見れたから
There are a lot of people there too.
人もいっぱいいるしね
Even the store staff gets angry.
店員さんにも怒られるし
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I wanted to do something a little naughty.
ちょっとエッチなことしたかったんだけどさ
I can't help it.
しょうがない
ERROR
じゃあさ、ホテル行っていい?
good?
いい?
Wait, there aren't that many people there.
ちょっとさ、あんまり人いないじゃん
You have vision.
視覚あるじゃん
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとおいでこっち
こっちちょっとおいで
ERROR
ちょっとここ座ってよ
Will it break?
壊れる?
It breaks.
壊れる
cute.
かわいい
Why do you still have that ticket?
なにそんなチケットを ずっと持ってんの?
It's a commemoration.
記念だなって
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
cute.
かわいい
It was a little boring.
ちょっとただた
No, I couldn't take a picture.
全然さ、 撮れなかったじゃん
Give me one more service shot.
もう一回サービスショットちょうだい
I guess I shouldn't have worn them.
履いてこなきゃよかったかなぁ
Come on, it's cute.
さあ、かわいいじゃん
cute.
かわいい
Were you a witch in high school?
高校のときに 魔女的存在だったの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Isn't she some kind of class witch?
なんかクラスの魔女的存在じゃないの?
No, nothing like that.
いや、 そんなことない
He was a bullied character.
いじられキャラだった
Was it a character that was teased?
いじられキャラだった?
That's a lie, right?
それは嘘でしょ
Really?
本当に?
Like a mood maker?
ムードメーカー的な?
yes.
そう
Really?
本当に?
ERROR
もうなんか男が黙ってた チワホヤされすぎて とかじゃないの?
That's not true.
そんなことない
Seriously?
マジで?
I see.
そっか
I wanted to be in the same age group and go to the same high school.
同じ年代の同じ高校に行きたかった
Really?
ホント?
Why didn't you come?
なんで来なかったの?
Well, first of all, we are of different ages.
いや、もうまず年代が違うよね
That's right.
そうだよね
Well then, let's continue the story.
じゃあまあさ、ちょっとさ、 話の続きとかはさ、
I guess I'll go to the hotel for a while and then go home.
ちょっと ホテル行って帰りにしようかな
I'll do it even if I change my mind.
聞い換わっちゃってもやるからさ
Shall we go to the hotel?
ホテル行こうか
good?
いい?
Do you want it again?
もう一回欲しいの?
I want it again.
もう一回欲しい
I want to pry it out.
こじこじ出したい
Is it because it doesn't hit hard?
こじこじ当たんないから?
Are there 5 types?
5種類あって?
There are 5 types.
5種類あって
It was difficult to choose 3 types, but I ended up with 2 types.
3種類こじこじだったけど、 2種類の方を出しちゃった
I see.
そっか
I'm not a big fan, so I only want to do it once.
こじこじじゃない方だから、 1回だけやりたい
Let's do it then.
じゃあしようか
Well, wait a minute.
じゃあちょっと待ってて
Reflect yourself like this.
こうやって自分映しといて
yourself?
自分を?
Selfie?
自撮り?
Please wait a moment while I exchange money.
両替してくるからちょっと待って
Money exchange?
両替?
I felt like a strange child all by myself.
一人で変な子みたいになっちゃった
一人で変な子みたいになってました
Seriously, really.
マジで本当に
Is it leaking?
漏 れてる?
It might be leaking a little.
ちょっと漏れてるかもしれない
Is it leaking?
漏れてる?
Wait, everyone is watching.
みんな見てるから待って
Say something.
一言言って
You can see it, right?
見えるでしょ?
I see too much of this.
見すぎちゃう、こっちを
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Did you get a cute photo?
可愛く撮れた?
It's probably leaking.
多分漏れてる
thank you.
ありがとうございます
May I?
いいですか?
Twice.
2回も
When you get out, do it properly.
出たら、 ちゃんと
That's the end, though.
もうそれで最後だよ、だけど
It's the last one.
最後だよ
What else should I do?
また、どうする?
It's better to have two types.
2種類の方がいいじゃん
Let's give up on that.
それはもう諦めよう
Because there are a lot of people.
人がいっぱいいるから
No, it's naughty, just show me your feet.
やだ、エッチ、足ばっかり映して
Give it to me, you naughty slut.
エッチなしらけ、ちょうだい
There are a lot of them, right?
いっぱいいるでしょ?
So, give it to me, you naughty slut.
だから、エッチなしらけ、ちょうだい
Um, no.
えっと、やだ
Where is it?
どこだっけ?
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいいるね
It's out, you little one.
出ました、こじこじ
Did it come out?
出たの?
You can guess.
当てていいよ
I could only show sex without it.
エッチなししか映せなかった
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
cute!
可愛い!
Well then, this again.
じゃあ、それまた、この
In your pocket?
ポケの中に?
Not much.
あんまり
Let me join you here.
ここに仲間入りさせてあげてよ
Can I join your group?
仲間入りできるかな?
See you later.
後でね
By the time I get home.
帰る頃に
good?
いい?
Were you satisfied?
満足できた?
Well then, that's enough.
じゃあ、もういいね
Let's go to the hotel.
ホテル行こう
I'm going.
行きます
You came to the hotel.
ホテル来たね
Why are you smiling so much?
なんで、そんなにこにこしてるの?
Finally.
ついに
It was long.
長かったわ
It was extremely long.
めちゃくちゃ長かった
It's been about a year since we met.
出会って1年くらいだから
About a year.
1年くらいね
You were annoyed, weren't you?
じらされたんだよね
I was teased, or rather, I couldn't perform because I was underage.
じらされたっていうか、未成年だから出演できなかった
I finally graduated from high school.
やっと高校卒業したからね
Legally?
合法的に?
oh yeah.
そうそう
It was fun just now.
さっき楽しかったね
it was fun.
楽しかった
Is it a character?
キャラクターなんだっけ?
Kojikoji?
コジコジ?
Is it popular?
流行ってんの?
There might be something like a bi-boom.
バイブームみたいなところあるかも
Who is the push girl?
押しの子ってやつ?
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
Who is the push character?
押しキャラクターってやつ?
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じ?
I see.
なるほどね
Uncle, I don't know much about that.
おじさん、その辺ちょっとわかんないからさ
I'll look into it later.
後で調べておこう
I followed it.
たどりました
I mean, she's a cool-headed type of girl.
コジコジ系女子ってことでね
That's right.
そうっすね
I agree.
そうだね
Cojicoji girl.
コジコジ女子ね
I'm glad you were able to take the picture.
よかったね、撮れてね
It was really good.
本当によかった
That was a bit of a shame though.
ちょっとあれは残念だったけどね
It's Jiro-kun.
ジローくんね
Is your name Jiro-kun?
ジローくんって言うの?
Yes, his name is Jiro-kun.
そう、ジローくんって言う
Well, then.
まあさ、じゃあさ
It was something I couldn't hear outside.
外で聞けなかったことだったりさ
I think I'll just ask about it.
ちょっと聞いていこうかなと思うんだけどさ
Go to the question corner.
質問コーナーへ
Question corner.
質問コーナー
copper?
どう?
Because the audience is watching.
視聴者さん見てるから
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいです
Question corner.
質問コーナーね
Have your boobs gotten a little bigger?
おっぱいちょっと大きくなった?
Well, maybe it's 1 cup bigger?
まあ1カップ大きくなったかな?
About.
ぐらい
lie?
うそ?
By the way?
ちなみに?
By the way, I have an E cup.
ちなみにEカップあります
E cup?
Eカップ?
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
I see.
そうか
Hey Perron.
ちょっとペロンって
Are you going to peron?
ペロンするの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
Ah, so cute.
あ、可愛い
What's that underwear?
何その下着?
I bought this for today.
これ、今日のために買った
Is that so?
そうなの?
Ah, just a little more.
あ、もうちょっと
It's true.
ほんとだ
It's a little big.
ちょっと大きい
Are you doing it?
やってる?
Yeah, it's big.
うん、大きい
Was it that big?
そんな大きかったっけ?
I think it has gotten really big.
マジ大きくなったと思う
lie?
うそ?
I feel like I have some meat on my stomach too.
お腹にもお肉ついた気がするけど
Do you feel like you have some meat?
お肉ついた気つるの?
lie?
うそ?
Me too, I've never seen anyone naked.
俺もさ、裸は見たことないからさ
That's it though.
あれ だけどさ
As expected.
さすがにね
Is that a big image?
そんな大きいイメージ?
Because I look small when I wear clothes.
服着てると小さく見えるから
Isn't that?
それ じゃない?
I've said it many times.
何度も言うけどさ
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
Wear a bag.
お袋をして
She's so cute, and her boobs are big.
そんな可愛くてさ、おっぱい大きくてさ
Hey, are you that male classmate?
ねえ、男の その同級生?
Yeah.
うん
That's already it, isn't it?
もうあれでしょ
Oh no, isn't that what it is?
ちやふや、それないの?
why?
なんで?
Is that so?
そうなの?
Do you have high ideals?
理想高いの?
No, I don't think it's expensive.
いや、高くないと思う
That's right.
そうなんだ
I see.
そっか
That's right.
そっかそっか
That's right, I guess.
そうなんだ、みたいなさ
That's right.
そうね
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I see.
なるほどね
Did you enjoy school?
学校楽しかった?
It was really fun.
めっちゃ楽しかった
What was fun?
何楽しかった?
Personally, I like eating KFC with friends on the way home.
個人的には、 帰り道で友達と食べる ケンタッキーが好きだ
It was.
った
I see.
なるほど ね
Is that so?
それであれ?
So you got a part-time job at Kentucky?
ケンタッキーのバイトしたってこと?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Really?
本当に?
Seriously?
マジで?
Kentucky, I have a part-time job.
ケンタッキーさ、バイトすんじゃん
Then can I eat Kentucky?
そしたらケンタッキー食えんの?
Can't I eat it?
食べれないかな?
It's a little cheaper.
ちょっと安くなるぐらい
It's a feeling.
気持ちね
That's like a 10 yen discount.
それが10円割引みたいな
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだね
That's right.
そう なんだ
It's cute.
かわいいね
So, how about eating around Kentucky?
じゃあ、ケンタッキー 食べ歩き?
Return?
帰 り?
That was fun.
そういうの楽しかったんだ
That's youth.
それ青春だね
I think it's the most youthful thing.
一番青春だと思う
However, I have only just graduated.
だけどさ、まだ卒業したばっかりじゃん
Not yet, but how do you feel about it?
まだだけど、実感っていうか どうなの?
No, not at all.
ない、全然ない
Today, I'm wearing casual clothes.
今日はさ、 私服じゃん
Next time, I think I'll take a photo in uniform.
次回さ、 制服で撮ろうかな
Bring your uniform, next time.
制服持ってきてよ、今度
Well, well, well, well.
まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ
Well, well, well, kind of.
まあ、まあ、まあ、まあみたいな
You can eat delicious sushi.
美味しいお寿司が食べれるだろう
Next is Yakiniku.
次は焼肉
次は焼肉ね
Next time, let's go to a yakiniku restaurant instead of all-you-can-eat.
次は食べ放題じゃない 焼肉屋行こうか
TRUE?
本当?
go.
行く
Can you bring it?
持ってきてくれる?
She's kind, honest, and cute.
優しいし、素直でかわいい
Well then, well then.
じゃあ、まあね
For now.
とりあえずさ
I'll do it even if I change my mind.
気持ち変わってもやるからさ
I'm about to take her to a hotel.
ホテル連れ込んだ手前があるから
I wonder if my lips should look like this.
くっちゃびりこんな感じでいいかな
yes.
はい
Okay, let's do it then.
よし、じゃあやっていこうか
You're wearing a hoodie.
パーカー着てるね
cute.
かわいい
Who is this?
誰これ?
Other people I don't know.
他に知らない人
It's not about my favorite fund or anything.
好きなファンドとかじゃなくて
I don't like it.
好きじゃない
Is it a little big?
ちょっと大きい?
It's a little big.
ちょっと大きいの
please show me.
見せてください
Did you take it off?
外しちゃった?
Show me well.
よく見せて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Could you help me out a little?
ちょっと手どけてくれるかな
Isn't it so beautiful?
めっちゃ綺麗じゃない?
Are you told?
言われる?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Not told.
言われない
How many cups is there?
何カップあんだっけ?
E cup.
Eカップ
Your voice is cute.
声かわいいね
May I ask you to remove it?
抜いてもらっていいかな
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
That's erotic.
エロいね
Take good care of it.
ちゃんと手入れしてて
Can I ask you to sit quietly one more time?
もう一回そっと座ってもらっていい?
By myself.
自分でさ
Can I spread it out for you?
広げてみせてもらっていい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
long?
長い?
long.
長い
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Shall we continue then?
じゃあ続きしようか
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Lick?
舐め?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Not too tight.
きつすぎない
It's so tight I can't put my finger in.
きつすぎて指が入んない
Shall we go again?
もう一回行っちゃうか
Can you please tell me how you feel?
俺の気持ちを伏してもらっていい?
Because I'll make it.
作るからさ
I have preparations.
準備あるんだ
From the finish?
仕上げから?
Erotic way of licking.
エロいね舐め方
What an amazing feeling.
すごい気持ち
fun?
楽しい?
It's been a while.
久しぶりだもんね
Can I change my position?
体勢変えていい?
Lick it gently.
優しく舐めてちゃ
Was it painful?
苦しかった?
Have you ever had it in your mouth?
口の中に出されたこととかある?
Isn't there?
ないの?
Be careful.
気を出して
Because it feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいからさ
Can I vomit now?
すぐ吐いていい?
I'll put it out.
出すよ
Can I have your hand with it just once?
一回ちょっと手に出してもらっていい?
Have you never had it?
飲んだことない?
Would you like to try it?
飲んでみる?
Did you drink it?
飲めた?
What did it taste like?
どんな味だった?
A little bitter.
ちょっと苦い
That's right.
そうだよね
how was it?
どうだった?
First time swallowing?
初ごっくん?
It hurts.
痛いですね
Look.
見て
I'm still fine.
まだ元気だよ
Continue?
続きする?
Can I take a loss next time?
今度損入していい?
What I just said is a mess.
さっき言ったばっかめちゃくちゃ
I can continue
続きできちゃう
hey.
ね
I want to do that.
あれ したい
Have you ever done that?
したことある?
Lie down, with your butt facing this way.
横になるから、 お尻こっちに向けて、
Get on top of me.
上に乗っておし
Hold your head over here, hold your butt over here.
こっちに、 頭を持って、 お尻をこっちに持って
It's so embarrassing.
すごい恥ずかしい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Stretch your shoulders.
肩を伸ばします
Can I have it raised?
上げてもらっていい?
Like that.
そんな感じで
Are you there?
いる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Not attached.
付けない
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
No?
ダメ?
No.
ダメ
I'll put it in.
入 れちゃう
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's tight and I haven't gone all the way yet.
きつくで、 まだ奥まで行ってない
I have to ring it a little slowly.
ちょっとゆっくり、 鳴らさないと
Are you trying to escape?
逃げようとしてる?
I want to match while looking at your butt.
お尻見ながら、 一致したいな
Turn to the other side?
反対側向ける?
Yeah.
うん
Get in
入れ
That's it.
ちゃ うね
I don't really do it.
あんまやらない
thank you.
ありがとう
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった
It felt a little good.
ちょっと気持ちよくて
Sorry, it came out while I was there.
ごめん、出ちゃった中に
Seno-chan.
せのちゃん
Sorry for creampie.
中出し、ごめん
It has been done.
されちゃった
First creampie?
初中出し?
First creampie.
初中出し
Sorry.
ごめんね
It was a good memory.
いい思い出になったね
Will you take pictures again?
また撮影してくれる?
good?
いい?
Shall we go eat after this?
この後、ご飯行こうか
Thank you.
ありがとうね
bye bye.
バイバイ
tired?
疲れた?
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was really fun.
めっちゃ楽しかった
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
Everything.
全部だね
I was tired, nervous, and had fun.
疲れたし、緊張したし、楽しかったし、
Like?
みたいな?
surely.
確かに
That's right.
そうだよね
Sorry.
ごめんね
When you're relaxing.
ゆっくりしてる時に
Thank you very much.
結構、ありがとうございます
These guys are the ones.
こいつらこそ
It was fun.
楽しかったね
Just like I said, let me take a picture of you in your uniform this time.
棒取れのさ、言った通りにさ、 今度は制服で撮らせてよ
Next time.
今度はね
Can I take a photo in uniform and then take another photo?
制服で撮って、 もう一回撮っていい?
good?
いい?
Today is today, I want your impressions.
今日は今日でさ、 感 想欲しいな、
Something like that.
みたいなさ
What are your thoughts, viewers?
感想っつうのさ、 視聴者さん?
Buyer?
購入者さん?
Sena-chan's work, to the buyers who buy this work.
せなちゃんのさ、 この作品を買ってくれる 購入者さんに向
So, I'd like to say a few words.
けて、 ちょっと一言欲しいな、 って思うからさ、
For buyers.
購入者さんに向けて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I have to look this way.
こっち見ないといけないですもんね
I'm watching, everyone.
見てるから、みんな
I'm looking at you through the screen right now, so our eyes meet.
画面越し今見てるから、 目合ってる状態
Do you see eye to eye?
目合ってる?
Ah, Senadesu.
あ、せなでーす
I'm waiting for your tearful report.
泣いた報告待ってます
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Do it properly.
ちゃんとしろよ
I agree.
そうだね
I want it done properly.
ちゃんとして欲しいね
I would like to see more comments like that.
そういうコメントいっぱい 触れ替えて欲しいね
I cried, like.
泣いたよー、みたいな
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It was fun, I guess.
楽しかったよー、みたいな
I hope that happens.
そうなればいいな
Let's take a photo again next time.
また今度撮影しようね
Thank you for today.
今日はありがたね
After this, let's go as promised.
この後、お約束の行こうか
Okay, okay.
よしよし
See you soon.
またねー